laylagrayce.com 2017-07-18

# Privacy Policy

### We value your privacy

Layla Grayce is committed not only to bringing you the finest products, but also to keeping your personal information confidential. We only require personal information from you when you place an order and will only use what you provide to process orders, ship orders and contact you if necessary. You may choose to sign up for our mailing list, but rest assured that we never share or sell your confidential information with any third parties. We compiled the following statements to explain how we collect, use and secure your information.

### Security Policy

We have taken every measure to ensure that online shopping at Layla Grayce is as secure as possible. We use Secure Socket Layering (SSL), the industry standard encryption technology that ensures safe transmission of your personal information. Once you enter the Checkout process (when you are ready to purchase the items you have put into your shopping cart), your connection to our server becomes secure. To confirm this, look at the bottom portion of your browser window. If you see an unbroken key or a closed lock (depending on your browser), you can be sure that your information is secure. You can also ensure security by checking the URL line in your browser. When you enter the secure area of our site, the first characters of the site address will change from “http” to “https”. If for some reason you do not see these cues, please contact us directly to place your order.

### About Cookies and JavaScript

“Cookies” are small amounts of data that are stored on your computer. They find their way to your browser via a web server. They sound friendly and helpful because they are. They flag information about your activity on our website, which helps us improve our site and make it friendlier and easier to use. We never use cookies to save passwords, credit card numbers or any other confidential information. Our website also requires that JavaScript is enabled on your browser. Our servers use JavaScript to provide a more interactive shopping experience. Enabling this coding language on your browser will not affect performance, nor will it collect or store any of your personal information.

### Personal information collected

Whenever you shop with Layla Grayce, we obtain information we need to complete your transaction. This may include your name, address, telephone number, email address and credit card number. We also keep records of your specific product purchases and transactions with us. We use this information to process your purchase transactions, send you marketing and promotional materials via email, and help us improve our online product assortments and services. You may always opt out of mailers, and we never share or sell any of our confidential customer information.

### Third Party Advertising Partners

Layla Grayce works with third-party partners, including Google, who automatically collect anonymous, non-personally identifiable information about your visit to our site. This information is collected using cookies. With these third-party partner tools, we receive data that allows us to provide you with improved services and site experiences. The anonymous information is used to analyze general patterns, trends and demographics of the customers who visit our website.

Information gathered may include, but is not limited to, age, gender, IP address, site navigation patterns, frequency of visits, and interests. Layla Grayce may use this information to inform, optimize and serve advertisements (banners and links) on third-party websites. This means we may create targeted advertisements on other websites for Layla Grayce products and services that are tailored to fit your interests. We will never run interest-based advertising campaigns that collect or disperse confidential information, such as email addresses, telephone numbers and credit card numbers. You can adjust your browser preferences to refuse all cookies of this kind, but doing so may limit our ability to provide an optimal and tailored shopping experience. If you wish to adjust your [Google Analytics](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/ "Google Analytics opt out") and [advertising settings](https://www.google.com/settings/u/0/ads?hl=en&sig=ACi0TCjs3rCXFJUAom--99bqgmrmSWv2rAWTmIpCHtquWLxkhKhP91Ap2qcx59F7vkCR5culipVSmaa2h62J7nAGwyHpwKgQhSVaDvy57Li8UGFLTKJEt-G_pwuf-C8ShpLL13wnhNoYQkFxbpbqBczw5UIhHdtXIe8FtlPdX1t5aqQm33JMt4dWqLQSwHA7JtDmQF3sYBs_q80uRpxlcotdNh-LBpxrFzEYCUeCkt7Uf0h7LNJ3kbjRA_4UFe2fZ1lOdfuTBk6rI3v6BtXQgb-xJcEF-w4TnQ "Google advertising settings"), please see their currently available opt-outs for the web.

### Online account registration

Registering at Layla Grayce makes your online shopping faster and easier. Your billing and shipping information is securely stored with us, so you won’t need to enter it each time you place an order. You will also be able to login to your account to check the status of your orders and your order history, as well as create a gift registry. You can add, delete or change your registered information at any time using your password.

### Opt out procedures

When you create a Layla Grayce account, complete an order, or sign up for newsletters, you provide us with your email address. Using this information, we send marketing emails about our products, services, contests and promotions that we feel may be of interest to you. We may also contact you with reminder emails about items you have left in your shopping cart. Each time you receive an email from us, you will be given the opportunity to opt out, or stop receiving them. Simply follow the unsubscribe link at the bottom of the email or contact us to remove your name from our mailing list. 

### Protecting children

We want to take special care to protect the safety and privacy of our children. Our website is not intended for use by, nor do we knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13. We urge parents and guardians to participate in their children’s online activities and use parental control or other filtering technology to supervise children’s access to the web.

### Links to other sites

We like to share information about other websites that we think our customers may be interested in. Layla Grayce is not responsible for these sites, so if you choose to check out their offerings and services, we suggest that you carefully review their privacy policies..

### Policy changes

Efforts to bring new services, ideas and partners to benefit our customers may make it necessary to amend our Privacy Policy. If this occurs, we will post the new policy on our website. Once posted, the new policy will go into effect immediately, replacing any previously stated policy. Our policy was last updated in December 2013.

### Contact Information

Feel like chatting? We’d love to hear your thoughts, comments and suggestions. Please contact us via email or call our customer service number. We look forward to hearing from you!

> Layla Grayce  
>  570 Colonial Park Dr, Ste 307  
>  Roswell, GA 30075
> 
> Phone: Phone: (770) 599-7896  
>  Fax: (770) 679-3354  
>  Email: [shop@laylagrayce.com](mailto:shop@laylagrayce.com)
